VIRGÍNIA VILHENA LADRA



Experience in cross-cultural communication as arts and cultural program manager. Creative producer for brazilian cultural institutional, in educational and sporting fields.

I am open to different jobs with enthusiasm, creative and attitude to learn and share!

Skills CS3 Softwares of image Photography Anthropology of childhood Portuguese [native] Spanish [fluent] English [advanced] Catalan [basic]



www.vivilhena.flavors.me/



br.linkedin.com/in/vivilhena

education

Oficial Master of Contemporary Art

University of Barcelona 2017 - studing

Postgraduated in Cultural Management SENAC - Brazil

2012 -2013

Bachelor Social Communication [Cine] FAAP - Brazil 2003 -2007

experience

Escola Mil.lenari

July -2017 - Art Monitor at the English Casal d'Estiu

Sellbytel

Jan/Apr -2017 - Technical Support Advisor for Android

Hostel Equit Point and Bar Avenue and Hideout - VGracia - Barcelona Oct/2016 - Dec/2016 - Breakfast and Cocktail Waitress

Cultural Manager at SESI-SP | BR

Apr/2014 - Sep/2016

Producer and Event coordinator at Agencia DAMA | BR 2013

Creative Producer at Galeria Amarelonegro de Arte Contemporanea | BR 2013

Cultural Manager for Digital Art at SESC-SP |BR 2010 -2013

Art & Exhibition Design, Scenography |BR 2008 -2012

TV Cultural, Disney Channel and freelancer

Barcelona | ES +34 662 055 568 vivilhena@gmail.com 34 years| single spanish and brazilian